<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaiyang Zhou&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kaiyang Zhou&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description> Efficient Adaptation of Large-Scale Models OV-DETR (ECCV&#39;22) CoCoOp (CVPR&#39;22) CoOp (IJCV&#39;22) Domain Generalization and Adaptation Survey (TPAMI&#39;22) DIDANet (TIP&#39;22) MixStyle (ICLR&#39;21) DAEL (TIP&#39;21) L2A-OT (ECCV&#39;20) DDAIG (AAAI&#39;20) Efficient Deep Learning OSNet (TPAMI&#39;21, ICCV&#39;19) DR-DSN (AAAI&#39;18) Scene Understanding PSG (ECCV&#39;22) Trustworthy Machine Learning EOW-Softmax (ICCV&#39;21) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misc</title>
      <link>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/misc/</guid>
      <description> Awesome tips on research, writing, presentation, etc. (by Jia-Bin Huang) Novelty in Science: A guide for reviewers (by Michael J. Black) How to Get Your CVPR Paper Rejected? (by Ming-Hsuan Yang) &amp;ldquo;In every life we have some trouble. But when you worry you make it double. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, be happy.&amp;rdquo; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>Call for Papers: IJCV Special Issue on The Promises and Dangers of Large Vision Models. (Paper submission deadline: March 1st, 2023.) Please follow my Twitter / Zhihu if you would like to receive the latest updates about my research and open-source projects.
Latest Papers On-Device Domain Generalization Domain Generalization: A Survey Panoptic Scene Graph Generation Neural Prompt Search Full-Spectrum Out-of-Distribution Detection Dynamic Instance Domain Adaptation Open-Vocabulary DETR with Conditional Matching Conditional Prompt Learning for Vision-Language Models Learning to Prompt for Vision-Language Models MixStyle Neural Networks for Domain Generalization and Adaptation Please visit my Google Scholar page for an up-to-date list of papers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Profile</title>
      <link>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/profile/</guid>
      <description>Short Bio (CV) Dr. Kaiyang Zhou is currently a Research Fellow at Nanyang Technological University, Singapore, working with Prof. Ziwei Liu and Prof. Chen Change Loy. He received his PhD (2020) in computer science from the University of Surrey, UK, under the supervision of Prof. Tao Xiang. His research lies at the intersection of machine learning and computer vision, with specialization in domain generalization, transfer learning, and efficient deep learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Google Scholar | Semantic Scholar | DBLP
2022 On-Device Domain Generalization
Kaiyang Zhou, Yuanhan Zhang, Yuhang Zang, Jingkang Yang, Chen Change Loy, Ziwei Liu
arXiv preprint, 2022
abstract | pdf | code
Domain Generalization: A Survey
Kaiyang Zhou, Ziwei Liu, Yu Qiao, Tao Xiang, Chen Change Loy
IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence (TPAMI), 2022
abstract | pdf | code
Learning to Prompt for Vision-Language Models
Kaiyang Zhou, Jingkang Yang, Chen Change Loy, Ziwei Liu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kaiyangzhou.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description> Nanyang Technological University Lecturer / Guest Lecturer
AI6126: Advanced Computer Vision (Topic: Open-World Visual Recognition) OpenMMLab Workshop: Object Detection Queen Mary University of London Teaching Assistant
ECS797: Machine Learning for Visual Data Analytics ECS708: Machine Learning </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
